export const QUIZ_DATA = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is Gender?',
      answer: 'a social and legal status, and set of expectations from society, about behaviors, characteristics, and thoughts. Each culture has standards about the way that people should behave based on their gender. This is also generally male or female. But instead of being about body parts, it’s more about how you’re expected to act, because of your sex.',
      options: [
        'a label — male or female — that you’re assigned by a doctor at birth based on the genitals you’re born with and the chromosomes you have. It goes on your birth certificate.',
        'a social and legal status, and set of expectations from society, about behaviors, characteristics, and thoughts. Each culture has standards about the way that people should behave based on their gender. This is also generally male or female. But instead of being about body parts, it’s more about how you’re expected to act, because of your sex.',
        'how you feel inside and how you express your gender through clothing, behavior, and personal appearance. It’s a feeling that begins very early in life.'
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What is Sex?',
      answer: 'a label — male or female — that you’re assigned by a doctor at birth based on the genitals you’re born with and the chromosomes you have. It goes on your birth certificate.',
      options: [
        'a label — male or female — that you’re assigned by a doctor at birth based on the genitals you’re born with and the chromosomes you have. It goes on your birth certificate.',
        'a social and legal status, and set of expectations from society, about behaviors, characteristics, and thoughts. Each culture has standards about the way that people should behave based on their gender. This is also generally male or female. But instead of being about body parts, it’s more about how you’re expected to act, because of your sex.',
        'how you feel inside and how you express your gender through clothing, behavior, and personal appearance. It’s a feeling that begins very early in life.'
      ]
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is Gender Identity?',
        answer: 'how you feel inside and how you express your gender through clothing, behavior, and personal appearance. It’s a feeling that begins very early in life.',
        options: [
          'a label — male or female — that you’re assigned by a doctor at birth based on the genitals you’re born with and the chromosomes you have. It goes on your birth certificate.',
          'a social and legal status, and set of expectations from society, about behaviors, characteristics, and thoughts. Each culture has standards about the way that people should behave based on their gender. This is also generally male or female. But instead of being about body parts, it’s more about how you’re expected to act, because of your sex.',
          'how you feel inside and how you express your gender through clothing, behavior, and personal appearance. It’s a feeling that begins very early in life.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is Heterosexual/Straight?',
        answer: 'A sexual orientation in which a person feels physically and emotionally attracted to people of a gender other than their own.',
        options: [
          'A woman whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same gender.',
          'A sexual orientation in which a person feels physically and emotionally attracted to people of a gender other than their own.',
          'A sexual and affectional orientation toward people of the same gender.',
          'A person whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same and other genders, or toward people regardless of their gender.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is Lesbian?',
        answer: 'A woman whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same gender.',
        options: [
          'A woman whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same gender.',
          'A sexual orientation in which a person feels physically and emotionally attracted to people of a gender other than their own.',
          'A sexual and affectional orientation toward people of the same gender.',
          'A person whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same and other genders, or toward people regardless of their gender.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is Gay?',
        answer: 'A sexual and affectional orientation toward people of the same gender.',
        options: [
          'A woman whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same gender.',
          'A sexual orientation in which a person feels physically and emotionally attracted to people of a gender other than their own.',
          'A sexual and affectional orientation toward people of the same gender.',
          'A person whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same and other genders, or toward people regardless of their gender.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is Bisexual?',
        answer: 'A person whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same and other genders, or toward people regardless of their gender.',
        options: [
          'A woman whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same gender.',
          'A sexual orientation in which a person feels physically and emotionally attracted to people of a gender other than their own.',
          'A sexual and affectional orientation toward people of the same gender.',
          'A person whose primary sexual and affectional orientation is toward people of the same and other genders, or toward people regardless of their gender.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is Gender Expression?',
        answer: 'How one expresses oneself, in terms of dress, mannerisms, and/or behaviors that society characterizes as “masculine” or “feminine.',
        options: [
          'People who do not subscribe to gender expressions or roles expected of them by society.',
          'A person whose gender identity and/or gender expression falls outside of the dominant social norm for their assigned sex, is beyond genders, or is some combination of them.',
          'How one expresses oneself, in terms of dress, mannerisms, and/or behaviors that society characterizes as “masculine” or “feminine.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is Genderqueer',
        answer: 'A person whose gender identity and/or gender expression falls outside of the dominant social norm for their assigned sex, is beyond genders, or is some combination of them.',
        options: [
          'People who do not subscribe to gender expressions or roles expected of them by society.',
          'A person whose gender identity and/or gender expression falls outside of the dominant social norm for their assigned sex, is beyond genders, or is some combination of them.',
          'How one expresses oneself, in terms of dress, mannerisms, and/or behaviors that society characterizes as “masculine” or “feminine.'
        ]
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is Gender Nonconforming?',
        answer: 'People who do not subscribe to gender expressions or roles expected of them by society.',
        options: [
          'People who do not subscribe to gender expressions or roles expected of them by society.',
          'A person whose gender identity and/or gender expression falls outside of the dominant social norm for their assigned sex, is beyond genders, or is some combination of them.',
          'How one expresses oneself, in terms of dress, mannerisms, and/or behaviors that society characterizes as “masculine” or “feminine.'
        ]
      }
]